http://www.creativecookware.com/terms_of_use/

DEAL OF THE WEEK
Giesser Messer 6 pcs Set HOLIDAY SPECIAL
$199.99 USD
reg. $299.99
Buy Now!
HOLIDAY FLASH SALE .... SAVE AN EXTRA 10% OFF YOUR PURCHASE TODAY Click for details
CART (0) |  MY ACCOUNT
AboutReviewsShipping PolicyHelpReturns & ExchangesContactOn Sale
AND/OR
Select Category ...
Woks / Stir Fry Pans
Select Brand ...
Zyliss
Select Price Range ...
Over $1000
(0)
Terms of Use
Terms of use:The following Terms of Use govern your access and use of this Web Site.Also, specific terms and conditions may apply to specific content, data, materials, or information contained on or available through this Web Site(the "Content") and to specific content, data, materials, or information youmay upload, submit and/or publish to the Web Site ("User Content") or transactions concluded through this Web Site. Such specific terms may be in addition to these Terms of Use or, where and then only to the extent expressly specified, may supersede these Terms of Use.Acceptance of Terms of Use: By accessing or using this Web Site you agree to be legally bound by the Terms of Use and all terms and conditions contained or referenced herein or any additional terms and conditions set forth on this Web Site. If you do NOT agree to all of these terms, you should NOT access or use this Web Site. We grant you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, personal, non-commercial license to access and use this Web Site. We reserve all right, title and interest not expressly granted under this license to the fullest extent possible under applicable laws.Modification of Terms:These Terms of Use may be amended by Creativecookware.com at any time. Such amended Terms of Use shall be effective upon posting. If you do not agree to, or cannot comply with, the Terms of Use as amended, you should not use this Web Site. By continuing to access or use the Web Site after such posting, you will be deemed to have accepted such amendments. You are advised to regularly review any applicable terms and conditions. Creativecookware.com reserves the right to discontinue or make changes or updates with respect to the Web Site or the Content of the Web Site at any time without notice. Creativecookware.com reserves the right to restrict, refuse or terminate access of any person to the Web Site or any part thereof effective immediately without notice at any time and for any reason whatsoever at its sole discretion.
Information collected:Non personally identifiable information: every time you visit the Creativecookware.com website, we may collect certain data that cannot be used to identify you and that concern the method you use to access our site. This may include your browser type and version, your Internet service provider, your IP address, and the search engine (if any) you used to find the site. This information helps us identify any issues with our server, administer the website and compile general site statistics. Creativecookware.com also collects certain details about your site visit. This allows us to determine which parts of our sites are most heavily visited, so that we can better tailor our sites to the needs and interests of our visitors.
Copyrights:
Copyright and all other proprietary rights in content provided by Creativecookware.com, its affiliates, subsidiaries, brand licensees and/or other partners, the software to operate and publish the Web Site, the compilation of data on the Web Site, and the order, sequence and arrangement of this Web Site, all belong to their specific brand company owner and / or its brand licensees, other partners or licensors. Product and company names and logos appearing on the Web Site may be registered or unregistered trade names, trademarks and service marks of their respective owners. Any use of the trade names, trademarks and logos displayed on the Web Site, except asexpressly provided in this Agreement, is strictly prohibited.
External links
Creativecookware.com websites contain links to other sites. Creativecookware.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or content of such sites. To protect your personal information, Creativecookware.com recommends that you read the privacy policy of every site you visit after clicking a link on a Creativecookware.com site.
Registration:
Opting in to email notifications may require you to register as a customer. This registration is free of charge. You can always decide to stop receiving communications from Creativecookware.com by following the opt out instructions in all our communications or by emailing us at order@creativecookware.com.
Passwords Only the unique password associated with the personal data file created when you register on the Creativecookware.com website can open this file. To protect the confidentiality of the data, do not reveal your password to anyone.
Our Products:
Prices for our products are subject to change without notice. We reserve the right at any time to modify or discontinue the Service (or any part or content thereof) without notice at any time. Creativecookware.com tries to ensure that the information posted on this Web Site is correct and up-to-date. However, the detail and accuracy of the images and specification that you see will depend on a number of factors, including your computer equipment and Internet connection. Creativecookware.com does not guarantee that the product images, available features, services or specifications displayed or described on the Web Site are or will remain accurate or complete. Further, Creativecookware.com reserves the right to change or make corrections to any of the information at any time and without prior warning, including to update the products, images, available features, services or specifications.
Online ordersPurchases placed online on our secure Web Site are cleared instantly and processed same day. There is NO minimum order required online. The SSL protocol (Secure Socket Layer, securing all exchanges on the Internet) is used for the full protection of the client’s information during his passage through the ''shopping cart'' so that your information remains confidential. We accept all major credit cards securely on our site. With the industry's most-advanced encryption, fraud prevention, and buyer protection policies, you can purchase with confidence.Returns and Exchanges:We will gladly accept any returns or If for any other reason you are not satisfied with your purchase, less shipping and handling fees (our actual cost to send you the goods.). You will need to send us back the package prepaid. If you had free shipping with your order and return any item you will be charged the exact shipping amount we paid to ship your order. Items must be in new and unused condition, with its original packaging. It can be returned within 90 days of purchase date with a Return Merchandise authorization number (RMA#). We are unable to accept unauthorized returns. In order to return any items you must email us at order@creativecoffee.ca to obtain a Return Merchandise Authorization number ( RMA# ) and instructions on where to send the package back to us. We will also need to know why the item is being returned. You will need to supply us with your name and order number. Allow 7 days before inquiring about return credits. Please clearly mark the return authorization number on the outside of your returned box.
Dispute Resolution:
If the laws of your jurisdiction of residence require that the laws of such jurisdiction or the courts of such jurisdiction apply (such as may be the case if you are a consumer residing in Quebec), such laws will apply and/or such claims will be resolved in such courts. To the extent permitted by law, these Terms of Use shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Province of Quebec, Canada, without reference to its conflict of laws provisions, and the federal laws of Canada applicable therein.
Notice of changes This privacy policy is subject to change at any time, in order to reflect the addition of website features and/or changes in the standards governing the handling of personal information online. In order for you to remain informed about the use of your personal information, our privacy policy will always be available on our websites. If we make major changes to the way in which we use your personal information, we will inform you by posting a prominently placed notice on our site.
About
Reviews
Shipping Policy
Help
Returns & Exchanges
Terms of Use
Contact
Sign-up
to get exclusive offers,
product info
&
discounts by email
Follow Us
© 2020 Creative Cookware. All rights reserved. Developed by Grafika Designs a Web Design company.
